Around the World
The kisses of the sun were sweet
I didn't blink
I let it in my eyes like an exotic dream
The radio playing songs that
I have never heard
I don't know what to say oh not another word
Just lah lah lah lah lah it goes around the world
Just lah lah lah lah lah it's all around the world
Just lah lah lah lah lah and everybody singing lah lah lah lah lah
And now the bells are ringing lah lah lah lah lah
Lah lah lah lah lah lah lah
Lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah
Inside an empty room my inspiration flows
Now wait to hear the tune around my head it goes
The magic melody you want to sing with me
Just lah lah lah lah lah the music is the key
And now the night is gone still it goes on and on so deep inside of me
I long to set it free
I don't know what to do just can't explain to you
I don't know what to say oh not another word
Just lah lah lah lah lah it goes around the world
Just lah lah lah lah lah it's all around the world
Just lah lah lah lah lah and everybody singing
Lah lah lah lah lah and now the bells are ringing
Lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah
The kisses of the sun
Around, around around, around around, around around, around
Lah lah lah lah lah it goes around the world
Just lah lah lah lah lah it's all around the world
Just lah lah lah lah lah and everybody singing lah lah lah lah lah and now the bells are ringing
Lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah lah